Guide to the Donald R. MacQuivey Papers M0834
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 9: Telecommunications General (Key Documents, etc.)
  - Chronology of Communications Satellite Events binder, 1945-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - documents re: Telecommunications, Washington, D.C., 1949-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - General Telecom (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1918-1956 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1940-1961 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1934-1965 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folders 9)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1965-1976 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Key Documents, 1965-1976 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Treaties A-H (Box 11, Folders 2)
  - Treaties I-N (Box 12, Folders 1)
  - Treaties O-Z (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Series 10: Telecommunications Chronological Files (Publications, Reports, Memoranda)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1957-1/1960 (Box 15, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 9/1960-10/1960 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 10/1960-3/1961, 9/1960-10/1960 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 3/1961-4/1961 (Box 8, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 5/1961-10/1961 (Box 9, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 10/1961-11/1961 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 11/1961-3/1962 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 3/1962-5/1962 (Box 19, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 5/1962-8/1962 (Box 20, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 9/1962-11/1963 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 9/1962-2/1963 (Box 14, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 2/1963 (Box 9, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 2/1963-4/1963 (Box 10, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 5/1963-6/1963 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 6/1963-8/1963 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 12/1963-1/1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1964 (Box 18, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1964-5/1964 (Box 19, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 6/1964-11/1964 (Box 22, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 11/1964-1/1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1965-4/1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 4/1965-10/1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 10/1965-12/1965 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 12/1965-3/1966 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 3/1966-10/1966 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 10/1966-11/1966 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 11/1966-12/1966 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 12/1966-6/1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 6/1969-2/1970 (Box 21, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 3/1970-5/1970 (Box 22, Folders 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 6/1970-2/1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 3/1971-12/1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1973-5/1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Chronological File 1/1975-7/1978, 1946-1971 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Chronological Document File, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Series 11: World War II/1940's
  - Harvard/MIT RRL (Radio Research Laboratory) Air Raid Precautions, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - RRL, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - RRL, 1942-1944 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - RRL Memoranda (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - RRL Termination Data (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Organization, 1942-1944 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Mission & Other Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - IMMRAN Group Photograph, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - RCM Correspondence, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - CBI Journal (DRM), 5-10/1944 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Customs (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Technical Observer, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Technical Reports, 1939-1945 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Aerial Photographs, 1940s (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - DRM "Moscow Diaries", 1946 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - China Burma India Journal, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Notes, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Series 12: DRM Personal Files
  - Bolinas, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Church, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Dormant Embryos, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Insurance (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - misc. personal material re: employment, retirement, etc., 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - memorabilia, 1920-1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - personal memorabilia, 1948-1984 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - personal correspondence re: Agnes Leeds, Merrill MacQuivey, PTA, Philosophical Society, Palo Alto, church, 1940s-1960s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - misc. personal correspondence, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - personal correspondence with Edith James (later MacQuivey) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - misc. personal correspondence, etc., 1975-1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Middlebury College Map (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Position Inquiries correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folders 3)
  - RCA Technical Lesson Student Binders (DRM), 1930s (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - RCA Technical Lesson Student Binders (DRM), 1930s (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Retirement, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1942-1945 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Self-Help (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - SRI, 1956-1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Stanford alumnus & employment (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Stanford correspondence, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Quad (inscribed by fellow students), 1931 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Souvenir Postcards, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - souvenirs, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Series 13: Media
  - Integrated Circuits Lab videocassette (U-matic), 1 videotape(s) (Box 2)
  - microfilm, slides (Box 88)
  - Misc. media: 3 computer tapes, 1 U-Matic videocassette, 10 audio cassettes, approx. 45 reels of audiotape (Box 93)